2551 N. Douglas Ave. Arlington Heights, IL 60004 (312) 282-6783 ♦ jaugent27@yahoo.com

M.B.A. graduate with excellent skill set in creating new opportunities, prospecting, relationship building, persuasion, and closing sales. I seek to find a position where I can utilize my CRM software knowledge and my large professional network that I have built through my work experiences and my M.B.A. interactions, as well as consistently attending networking events in person and online, to build a large sales pipeline in the high-technology industry.

EDUCATION

M.B.A.

DePaul University, Kellstadt Graduate School of Business, Chicago, Illinois. 2009

B.S., Business Entrepreneurship

Indiana University, Kelley School of Business, Bloomington, Indiana. 2000

EXPERIENCE

Director

Baker Tilly, Chicago, Illinois, Full service business management consulting firm Nov 2011-Feb 2013

- Responsible for business development efforts for the Growth Strategies group
- Manage multiple sales channels including salesforce.com account executives, internal firm partners, existing firm clients, and professional networks
- Communicate the value and capabilities of the firm to clients and prospects
- Cultivate, qualify and pursue leads, including assisting in proposal creation, building relationships with decision makers, and managing the sales process to a close
- Have established a very large network of contacts at salesforce.com within the Central region and beyond. This
 network exists of Commercial and Enterprise account executives, Regional and Area vice presidents, Alliance
 managers and many others.
- Extensive knowledge and experience developing a successful partnership with salesforce.com

Practice Development Manager

sakonent, Chicago, Illinois, CRM 2.0 Consultancy Oct 2009-Nov 2011

- Sold CRM consulting, implementation, and outsourcing services exclusively for salesforce.com solutions
- Worked on a daily basis with salesforce.com AE's through the sales process from initial interest through to close and beyond
- Have created numerous strong strategic alliances with Account Executives from salesforce.com
- Extremely knowledgeable with the functionality of salesforce.com, as well as the CRM landscape in general
- Prospected for clients by cold calling, canvassing at trade shows, and most often, networking, allowing me to mostly field calls from salesforce AE's bringing me into deals.
- Traveled to client sites to sell consultatively and participate in requirements gathering
- Assisted in creating comprehensive proposals and completing RFP's
- Attended industry events to network, prospect, and learn new standards and practices.
- Closed \$2.5 million of services business in 2011

Business Development Manager

Safepole LLC, Chicago, Illinois, Privately Owned Medical Products Company 2006-2009

- Created sales strategy for start-up medical products company; Contacting and following up with hundreds of hospital leads
- Built a solid strategy to sell Safepole into hospitals; determined how to shorten the typically long sales cycle
- Communicated through multiple levels in chain of command; Sought out product advocate within prospected company to help push sale to close.
- Built and managed relationships through channel sales partners.
- Grew sales 275% from 2008 revenues.

Jason Ugent

2551 N. Douglas Ave. Arlington Heights, IL 60004 (312) 282-6783 ♦ jaugent27@yahoo.com

Managing Director

Prime Properties Group, Inc., Chicago, Illinois 2005-2009

- Created a niche business rehabbing and building homes in the NW Indiana region
- Researched and developed a specific approach to buying distressed properties
- Made many great relationships with agencies and banks to facilitate success in each aspect of the business

Software Sales Executive

GL Trade, Chicago, Illinois Public Company Headquartered in France 2004-2005

- Sold SaaS and on-premise financial software. Solved the problem of communicating with fast-paced decision makers.
- Built relations with hedge funds, broker/dealers, proprietary trading groups, banks, and other financial institutions.
- Maintained strong relationships with C-level executives at financial institutions to sell full suite of software products.
- Created proposals and negotiated contracts to meet sales quotas.
- Exceeded quota each month due to relentless prospecting and a deep pipeline.
- Closed a large six-figure deal within first month at the company. Client grew to be the largest of the Chicago
 office.

Trader

Kottke Associates, Chicago Board of Trade, Chicago, Illinois 2001-2004

- Traded a proprietary futures account.
- Made split second decisions in a very pressured environment to buy or sell Dow and S&P futures contracts.
- Developed a trading strategy that incorporated current market trends both on a large scale and specific to the index being traded that allowed me to have an advantage in order to take profits.
- Created many relationships with traders, clearing firms, and executives in the financial industry.

Business Development Manager

Platinum Golf and Logo, LLC, Chicago, Illinois 2000-2001

- Created business plan to target corporate gift market; Prepared financial plan; negotiated costs and contracts.
- Responsible for execution of plan and daily operations of company including: sales calls, supplier relationships, advertising efforts, product research, and market research.
- Developed marketing strategy and sales plan; promoted product ideas to corporate clients; managed corporate relationships.

ACTIVITIES

Vice President, Idea Creation and Executing, Graduate Entrepreneurs' Organization (GEO), DePaul University 2009

- Create and execute events for newly formed student organization. Strategize best approach to grow and attract members.
- Network with local entrepreneurs, professors, students, and other collegiate entrepreneurial organizations to determine meaningful activities and events.

The Second City, Chicago, Illinois 2000-2002

- Member of comedy improvisation team; Successfully completed five training levels over multi-year period
- Advanced my sales skills; Cultivated my presentation and persuasion abilities; Refined my closing proficiencies.

Finalist, Business Plan Competition, Center for Entrepreneurship, Indiana University Kelley School of Business. 1999

• Selected as one of six finalists out of 50, for development and presentation of an original business plan.